
  {
    "questions": [

    {
      "question": "Which of these is a conditional statement?",
      "answers": [
        "When the green flag is clicked, turn 15 degrees",
        "Forever move 11 steps",
        "If i snap my fingers",
        "Repeat 10 times"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
      {
        "question": "What  is the name for a character in Scratch?",
        "answers": [
          "Character",
          "Sprite",
          "Scratcher",
          "Cather"
        ],
        "correctIndex": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a menu in Scratch?",
        "answers": [
          "Variable",
          "Go",
          "Looks",
          "Motion"
        ],
        "correctIndex": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "What  is a Sprite called in Scratch?",
        "answers": [
          "Musician",
          "Variable",
          "Dancer",
          "Actor"
        ],
        "correctIndex": 3
      },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is not a type of computer programming language?",
      "answers": [
        "Coffee",
        "Java",
        "Javascript",
        "Python"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What  is a Variable?",
      "answers": [
        "This is a temporary memory space that stores information",
        "A name assigned to a memory space",
        "An identifier used to call a data",
        "A player that jumps"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What  is Computer Code",
      "answers": [
        "A group of English words",
        "A set of rules that tells the computer what to do",
        "A set of instructions that are made up of words and numbers in the right order",
        "A step by step way of eliminating problems"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },

    {
      "question": "What is the physical part of a computer system?",
      "answers": [
        "Software",
        "Hardware",
        "Softcopy",
        "Hardcopy"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Function names are always followed by parentheses ",
      "answers": [
        "False",
        "True"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": " _______ is how we write code",
      "answers": [
        "Syntax",
        "Variables",
        "Loops",
        "Function"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {

      "question": " A computer cannot understand the directions of code even if there is a mistake in the syntax? ",
      "answers": [
        "True",
        "False",
        "Inbetween",
        "Both"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0
    }
]
}
